# ADRIANA GUERRA

adriana.luz.guerra@gmail.com 📞 +1 949 763 8167 (im) linkedin.com/in/a-l-guerra





#### SKILLS

- JavaScript
- VB
- C#
- ASP.NET
- .NET Framework
- .NET CORE
- HTML
- CSS
- SQL
- VBA

# **EDUCATION UC BERKELEY**

**BA** in Cognitive Science

## **SOFT SKILLS**

- Leadership
- Teaching/Mentoring
- Troubleshooting
- Communication

#### LANGUAGES

- English: Native
- Spanish: Fluent
- French: Proficient

# **ADDITIONAL**

**US** Citizen References and additional experience available upon request.

### **PROFILE**

I am a self-motivated developer dedicated to the pursuit of well-designed software and systems. Working in a variety of fields, from SCUBA diving to neuroscience research, has given me the opportunity to develop strong skills in the interpretation of user needs and to apply my development skills to wide a variety of projects. I am interested in developing efficient systems that are userfriendly and versatile.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# SOFTWARE DEVELOPER • Bubble Manager & Bubble Cert, Aug 2017 - Present

- With a partner, developed customized SaaS business management software for SCUBA centers using MS Access and VBA that is currently used at 19 centers in 4 countries.
- Streamlined the customer registration process through a dynamic and responsive web-form using ASP.NET, C#, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and JQuery.
- Simplified customer enrollment with international SCUBA agencies by posting customer data directly to dive agency web-servers from the business management system using VBA and WinHTTP requests.
- Developed Batch and PowerShell scripts to automate the data management software installation and configuration.
- Built a web-app for SCUBA instructors and SCUBA centers using ASP.NET, .NET Framework, VB.NET, SQL, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, AJAX, and REST API to simplify the registration and certification of students with international SCUBA agencies.

# PROGRAM COORDINATOR • Roctopus Pro Center, Thailand, Jun - Sep 2018

- Reorganized and oversaw a SCUBA professional training program.
- Developed a training schedule to maximize opportunities for trainees while minimizing redundant work for limited staff.
- Created Google Sheet and Google Script based program management tools to track student training progress easily.
- Updated design and content of the website using WordPress and Google Analytics.
- Developed email templates using HTML and CSS.
- Oversaw social media and responded to program inquiries.

# SCUBA INSTRUCTOR • Sairee Cottage Diving, Thailand, Nov 2013 - Jan 2018

- Worked as a head SCUBA instructor at a SCUBA resort in one of the busiest diving destinations in the world.
- Taught students of all levels, from introductory experiences to courses for aspiring professionals.
- Received 5 student-elected PADI recognition awards for my teaching.
- Organized SCUBA trips and mentored interns while teaching courses.

# STAFF RESEARCH ASSOCIATE • UC San Diego, Sep 2010 - Aug 2012

- Worked with the Research on Aging and Development Lab and the Swartz Center for Computational Neuroscience.
- Collected neurobehavioral measures (i.e. electroencephalography, eye tracking, body-motion capture, and behavioral tests) from typical and clinical populations.
- Analyzed data using specialized software.
- Developed protocols and Python scripts to test the accuracy of datastream integration from data sources with varying sampling rates.